Hello, I am Savita Maiti,
I am an advisor [ __ ]
product manager at ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company. Today I will
discuss a term plan with you. The
name of this plan is ICI Pru I Protect
Super.
We know that there is no return on term plans,
but through this plan, if
we want, we can also get a return on money.
Before talking about this plan, I did not say a few words.
This plan is a
modern plan that the company has brought to the market.  The reason for this is that
accidents are currently increasing.  People's lives are
now suffering from uncertainty.
Because today, when we leave the house in the morning to go to
work, there is no guarantee that we will return at the end of the day.
So
when it appears that someone in the house is earning an
income.  There are
elderly parents and a wife at home.
They have expenses.
There are small children.  They have studies.
So, saving money after meeting all these expenses, good and bad,
becomes very stressful.  Maybe
a little bit can be saved.   As
long as I'm in this bag, I can carry on with everything.
But
what would happen to the family if something suddenly happened?  So
this plan is made with family in mind.   To
take this plan, you must be between
18 and 55 years of age.  That is, only those who are between the
ages of 18 and 55 years can
take this plan.  With this plan,
we will always know that we are
leaving 50 lakh rupees for the family.  That means, even
if something happens to me, my family will immediately
receive 50 lakh rupees.
And through this plan,
if I fall
ill and two registered
doctors have prescribed that I should eat good food for another six months,
then I will
get 50 lakh rupees while I am still alive.
And if I become physically disabled, then the remaining
premium will be the amount I have paid
and the remaining
premium will be waived.
To take this plan, you must have passed HS.
Annual income must be 3 lakh taka.
And here,
ITR filing is not required
and there is exemption for the tenant.
Through this plan, we will
get all these facilities.  But yes,
if I think
I don't want to keep this coverage after going to the doctor, then
I can withdraw my payment through Smart Exist.
That was the feature of this plan.
If you like it, be sure to
like and share it.  You should
take this plan thinking of your family
and if you want to settle with this plan, then
definitely
call me on this number 943479989.  Thank you.